startv.com 2015-09-15

# 

**Privacy Policy**

Effective July 11, 2014 

**1\. INTRODUCTION**

Star India Private Limited (“Star” or “we”) wants you to be familiar with how we collect, use, and disclose information from and about you. This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with information collected through services such as our website, www.startv.com, and any associated mobile sites, applications (“apps”), or widgets (collectively, the “Star Services”). By using the Star Services, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. A list of our affiliated companies (“Company Affiliates”) is available at www.21cf.com.

As set forth in our [Terms of Use](http://us.startv.com/starplustandc/tesrmsofuse.aspx) , The Star Services are for a general audience, are not targeted to children, and do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. 

This Privacy Policy applies to all users of Star Services and to Star’s collection and use of your personal information (i.e., information that identifies a specific person, such as full name or email address). It also describes generally Star’s practices for handling non-personal information (for example, interests, demographics and services usage). 

**2\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

Star and our service providers collect the following information from and about you: 

**Registration Information** is the information you submit to participate in a Star Service, for example, to enter a contest or sweepstakes. Such information may include, for example, name, sex, residential address, contact details, and email address.

**Public Information and Posts** consist of comments or content (such as poll voting or quiz answers) that you post to the Star Services and the information about you that may accompany those posts or content, which may include a name, user name, comments, likes, status, profile information and picture. Public Information and Posts are always public, which means they are available to everyone and may be displayed in search results on external search engines. 

**Information from Social Media**. If you access or log-in to a Star Service through a social media service or connect a Star Service to a social media service, the information we collect may also include your user ID and/or user name associated with that social media service, any information or content you have permitted the social media service to share with us, such as your profile picture, email address or friends lists, and any information you have made public in connection with that social media service. When you access the Star Services through social media services or when you connect a Star Service to social media services, you are authorizing Star to collect, store, and use such information and content in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Activity Information**. When you access and interact with the Star Services, we may collect certain information about those visits. For example, in order to permit your connection to the Star Services, our servers may receive and record information about your computer, device, and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. If you access the Star Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device, geolocation data, or other transactional information for that device. 

Cookies and other tracking technologies (such as browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe Flash technology including cookies) are comprised of small bits of data that often include a de-identified or anonymous unique identifier. Websites, apps and other services send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer so the website can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that service. These technologies may also be used to collect and store information about your usage of the Star Services, such as pages you have visited, content you have viewed, search queries you have run and advertisements you have seen. 

Third parties that support the Star Services, by serving advertisements or providing services, such as allowing you to share content or tracking aggregate Star Services usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect similar information. Star does not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies. For more information about third-party advertising networks and similar entities that use these technologies, see www.aboutads.info/consumers, and to opt-out of such ad networks’ and services’ advertising practices, go to www.aboutads.info/choices.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information. Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe’s website, see http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/ help/settings_manager.html. Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features, content or personalization available through the Star Services.

**Information from Other Sources.** We may supplement the information we collect with information from other sources, such as publicly available information from social media services, commercially available sources and information from our Company Affiliates or business partners.

By using the Star Services, you affirmatively understand, agree and consent that any collection, storage, and processing, of your information that may occur is for a lawful purpose and is considered necessary for Star to provide the Star Services.

**3\. USE AND DISCLOSURE**

We use the information we collect from and about you to provide the Star Services and features to you, including: to measure and improve those Star Services and features; to provide you with the latest updates on our channels and programming; to improve your experience with both online and off-line Star Services by delivering a customized experience and content you will find relevant and interesting, including advertising and marketing messages; to allow you to comment on content, and participate in online games, contests, sweepstakes, polls, or quizzes; to provide you with customer support and to respond to inquiries. When the information collected from or about you does not identify you as a specific person, we may use that information for any purpose or share it with third parties.

We use the information we collect from and about you for these additional purposes. By using the Star Services, you affirmatively understand, agree and consent that use of your information for these additional purposes is lawful and is considered necessary for Star to provide the Star Services.

To allow service providers to assist us in providing and managing the Star Services. Star may make your information available to certain third party service providers, such as contractors, agents or sponsors, who help us manage or provide the Star Services. 

To allow social sharing functionality. If you log in with or connect a social media service account with Star Services, we may share your user name, picture, and likes, as well as your activities and comments with other Star Services users and with your friends associated with your social media service. We may also share the same information with the social media service provider. By logging in with or connecting your Star Services account with a social media service, you are authorizing us to share information we collect from and about you with the social media service provider, other users and your friends and you understand that the social media service’s use of the shared information will be governed by the social media service’s privacy policy. If you do not want your personal information shared in this way, please do not connect your social media service account with your Star Services account and do not participate in social sharing on Star Services.

To provide sponsored and co-branded services and features. We may offer sponsored and co-branded services, promotions or features, such as contests, sweepstakes or other promotions together with a sponsor or third party partner (“Co-Branded Services”). These Co-Branded Services may be hosted on Star Services or on the sponsor/third party’s service. By virtue of these relationships, we may share the information you submit in connection with the Co-Branded Service with the sponsor or third party. The sponsor or third party’s use of your information will be governed by the sponsor or third party’s privacy policy. 

To deliver relevant advertisements. Star and our service providers may use the information we collect from and about you to deliver relevant ads to you when you use the Star Services or another service. As noted above, third-party advertising networks and advertisers may use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track information such as demographic information, inferred interests, aggregated information, and activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests. To find out more about third-party advertising networks and similar entities that use these technologies, see www.aboutads.info, and to opt-out of such advertising networks’ and services’ advertising practices, go to www.aboutads.info/choices. 

To contact you. Star may periodically send promotional materials or notifications related to the Star Services. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials, you can follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. There are certain service notification emails that you may not opt-out of, such as notifications of changes to the Star Services or policies. 

To share with our Company Affiliates, Subsidiaries, or Join Ventures. Star may share your information with Company Affiliates, subsidiaries and joint ventures for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. A link to a website that lists Company Affiliates can be found at the beginning of this policy. Users who visit Company Affiliates’ services should still refer to their separate privacy policies, which may differ in some respects from this Privacy Policy. 

To share with business partners. Star may share your information with business partners to permit them to send you marketing communications consistent with your choices. 

To protect the rights of Star and others. There may be instances when Star may in its sole discretion disclose your information, including situations where Star has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of Star, our Company Affiliates, Subsidiaries, Joint Ventures or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety, privacy, and security of users of the Star Services or members of the public, such as when we believe disclosure is necessary to prevent imminent harm, financial loss, or suspected illegal activity; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; (iv) comply with the law or legal process; or (v) respond to requests from public and government authorities, including in connection with investigations relating to fraud, intellectual property infringement, or other unlawful activities. 

To complete a merger or sale of assets. If Star sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, Star may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction. The new entity will follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.

**4\. SECURITY**

Star uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. However, no one can guarantee the complete safety of your information. 

**5\. USER ACCESS AND CONTROL**

If you would like to review, correct, update, suppress, or otherwise limit our use of personal information you have previously provided directly to us, you may contact us using the mechanisms provided below. In your request, please include your email address, name, address, and telephone number and specify clearly what information you would like to change, update, or suppress. Before fulfilling your request we will take steps to verify your identify. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. You may also request that we not share your personal information on a going-forward basis with Company Affiliates or unaffiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes by sending an email to unsubscribe@startv.com with “Disclosure Opt-out” in the subject line and your full name, email address, and postal address in the body of the email. We will try to comply with your request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable. 

**6\. OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION** Updates to Privacy Policy. Star may modify this Privacy Policy. Please look at the Effective Date at the top of this Privacy Policy to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Star Services. 

Location of Data. The Star Services are hosted in and managed from India. By using the Star Services, you understand and consent to having any personal information processed in India and stored on servers in different countries around the world. Indian data protection and other relevant laws may not be the same as those in your jurisdiction. This includes the use of cookies and other tracking technologies as described above. As a result, please read this Privacy Policy with care.

Linked Services. The Star Services may also be linked to sites operated by unaffiliated companies, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, products or subscriptions, games, newsletters, contests or sweepstakes, or applications developed and maintained by unaffiliated companies. Star is not responsible for the privacy practices of unaffiliated companies, and once you leave the Star Services or click an advertisement you should check the applicable privacy policy of the other service. 

Data Retention. We will retain your information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or allowed by law. 

Remember that even after you have requested deletion of your information stored by Star, copies of some your information may remain viewable in some circumstances where, for example, you have shared information with social media or other services. Because of the nature of caching technology, your information may not be instantly inaccessible to others. We may also retain backup information related to you on our servers for some time for fraud detection or to comply with applicable law or our internal security policies. It is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information due to technical constraints, contractual, financial or legal requirements. 

Sensitive Information. We ask that minors under the age of 18 do not submit any personal information to us. We ask that all users not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive personal information (such as social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic or communal origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the Star Services or otherwise.

7\. CONTACT US

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

Email: hello@startv.com  
Mail: 21st Century Fox Star US LLC  
1185 Avenue of the Americas, 22nd Floor  
New York, NY 10036
